myoave.com 2013-04-06

# OceanAvenue.com - Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY

Ocean Avenue is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We have taken great efforts to keep your information confidential and secure at all times within our system. This Privacy Policy explains what we do with the personal information that we collect from you. Please read the following to understand our practices regarding personal information and how they affect you as you use our products and services. This statement discloses our current privacy practices; if we make material changes to these practices, we will announce them.

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

Generally, you can visit the oceanavenue.com website without entering any personal information. The oceanavenue.com website collects personal information such as name, mailing address, billing address, email address, phone number, credit card number and its expiration date should you choose to become an Ambassador or Customer as this information is necessary for us to complete the transaction and notify you of your order status.

To access most of the functionality at oceanavenue.com and make a purchase, we require that you become a registered user and agree to comply with the terms of either our Ambassador and/or Customer Agreement. You must also choose a unique username and password to access your account. To become a registered user, we require that you provide your name, and valid and current email address, so that we may contact you, when necessary, concerning activity that is relevant to your account.

For Ocean Avenue Ambassadors, the main purpose of the oceanavenue.com website is to manage your business, personally sponsored Customers, and your downline. In order to use the oceanavenue.com website, you must have a Login provided by Ocean Avenue. When enrolling to become a Ocean Avenue Ambassador and thereby obtain access to oceanavenue.com, we collect personal information, including your name, home or business address, telephone numbers, email address, IP address, credit card number and expiration date, bank account information (for direct deposit or direct debit), and various government-issued identifying data, including, but not limited to, your passport number, tax identification number, national ID card number, social insurance number, etc. We may also collect scanned copies of government-issued photo I.D.'s. This data is necessary to manage your Ocean Avenue business for purposes of identifying who you are, placement of you and of your downline, compliance management, product ordering, recognition and rewards, and bonus calculation and payment. We permit your upline to see only your name. We permit your Sponsor to see your name, email address and phone number. We also collect third party personal information from Customers, including their name, address, telephone number, email address, and credit card number and expiration date. 

**How We Use Your Information**

We conduct research on our Ambassador and/or Customers demographics, interests, and behavior based upon the information you provide us when you register or participate in contests or other promotions on our site, or based upon the information on our server log files. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. We may also notify you of products, services, or areas of our site that we think may interest you based on the information we've received. We may use your email address, mailing address and/or phone number to provide quality customer support or to reach you regarding order status, product or fulfillment issues and other customer service related activities. We may use your email address, mailing address and/or phone number to contact you regarding new product offerings, newsletters and other aspects of your use of the Ocean Avenue website. If, however, you do not wish to receive such communications, you have the ability to "opt-out" at any time and you will not be contacted further.

**Information Sharing**

Ocean Avenue is not an "information broker." We do not engage in the selling of the profile, contact, web usage habits, behavior, buying patterns, or demographic information of our customers, partners or users. We use the information we collect about you to process orders, pay bonuses and provide the best and most personalized service possible. We may revise this Privacy Policy occasionally, so please check it frequently. Ocean Avenue does not share, sell, rent, or trade personal information with third parties other than as described in this privacy policy.

**Agents/Service Providers**

We use third parties such as a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. When you purchase a product and use our site, we will share your name, address, telephone number, and email address as necessary for the third party to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for promotional purposes.

**Legal Disclaimer**

In addition to the circumstances described above, Ocean Avenue may disclose or release information when we, in good faith, believe that doing so is reasonably necessary: (i) to comply with the law, judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site; (ii) to enforce or apply the terms of User Agreement; or (iii) to protect the rights, property or safety of Ocean Avenue Sites, our users, or others.

**Tracking Information**

Your Web browser or email application automatically provides your Internet Protocol address ("IP address") to other computers with which you communicate over the Internet, so that they know where to send you information.

We receive an IP address each time you view one of our Web pages, because the browser automatically reports it to us. We may use IP addresses for various purposes, including:

  * Diagnosing service or technology problems. 
  * Assessing and maintaining system security.
  * Displaying the most appropriate advertising or content. 
  * Studying how people use our site and how we can improve it. 
  * Reporting to advertisers about aggregate, but not individual, information derived from IP addresses. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small piece of information that is stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. The Ocean Avenue Website utilizes cookies for the sole purpose of uniquely identifying our users and securing their personal information. We also use cookies to track your order process without requiring reentry or re-verification of password or personal information on each page of the site. Rather than storing this information on Ocean Avenue's server, the cookie is stored in your computer and is activated only when you visit the Ocean Avenue Sites. Your privacy and security are not compromised when you accept a cookie from the Ocean Avenue Sites. No one can access the information except Ocean Avenue.

**Email & "Opt Out" Policy**

We may use your email address provided to contact you regarding the following:

  * User Registration Status (including confirmation of account signup);
  * Order Status and Shipping Notification
  * Online Customer Satisfaction Survey
  * Major changes to the website, addition of new products or services;
  * Promotional and marketing materials that we think you may find useful.

If you desire not to receive information about products or services we think may be of interest, you can change the notification options in your account settings. If you wish to not receive any of these emails, you may opt-out by submitting your email address to [ membersupport@oceanavenue.com](mailto:membersupport@oceanavenue.com) or by following the unsubscribe instructions within each email communication.

**Protecting Your Personal Information**

The Ocean Avenue Sites use secure sockets layer (SSL) to encrypt the transfer of sensitive information, such as your account password and billing information including credit card, from your web browser to our web server.

Only the last four (4) digits of your credit card number will be displayed in your account. Emails you send to us may not be secure unless otherwise told that security measures will be in place prior to your transmitting the information. For this reason, we ask that you do not send confidential information such as credit card numbers or account numbers to us through emails.

The same SSL protocol also acts to authenticate the Ocean Avenue Sites and prevent unauthorized "hackers" from masquerading as any of our sites while you are logged in to your account. This is accomplished through a "digital certificate", which is an unforgettable electronic "identity card".

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**

By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by Ocean Avenue as described in this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions regarding Ocean Avenue's privacy policy and practices, please mail to:

Ocean Avenue, LLC.  
Attention: Legal Department  
10701 S River Front Parkway, Suite 110

South Jordan, Utah 84095

Email to: [privacy@oceanavenue.com.](mailto:privacy@oceanavenue.com)
